{
    "id": "9a50fb201a0943419e88c9d6c06baadd",
    "title": "Too, Too Much, Too Many",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is ……………. young to know better.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too…to.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "134205c1151c4f689079e380e9631344"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is far …………… hot to go out now.",
            "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9722b336de594040bd23d9e705c49df3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived …………….. late to watch the show.",
            "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8be73c2257774def968d3138d6b6cbe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ……………. early for the shops to be open.",
            "description": "We cannot use too much before adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "974f00a9b6e242a280176b153aee0d04"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea is too hot …………..",
            "description": "Objects are usually omitted after the infinitive in this construction.",
            "answers": [
                "to drink",
                "to drink it",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b99883e2920b497d9dd355efa00bc00c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea is too hot for us …………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are possible after the infinitive in structures with for.",
            "answers": [
                "to drink",
                "to drink it",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db561b8d067c47c89200eb3c2a5459c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ……………… young to live on your own.",
            "description": "Most expressions that can modify comparatives can also modify too.",
            "answers": [
                "far too",
                "far too much",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f175ea7336a04df3b3047ce923725f60"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could not lift the bag because it was ………………. heavy.",
            "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c98f3a1e8a74854a6f320b954063a3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He does not like …………………..",
            "description": "We cannot use too before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "women who are too tall",
                "too tall women",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "382c33e8372e46908916da9e7b7e6095"
        },
        {
            "question": "You put ……………… sugar in the tea.",
            "description": "We use too much before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab9180e360914212af8d98eeb2e818de"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am getting ……………….. calls from marketers these days",
            "description": "We use too many before countable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "too many",
                "too much",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bed93fdafd4a46499b8d4e402b3de655"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will look more beautiful if you stop wearing ……………….. make-up.",
            "description": "We use too much before uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "efec5a4cb9c74b97b015b981fdad38e0"
        }
    ]
}